$PAGE0	Monitored Stats
$LASTCHANCE	Are you sure?
$REREGISTER	Actor Events re-registering actors
$REMOVEWARN	This will remove this regestered event. The mod associateed with the monitored event WILL STOP WORKING. Are you sure you want to do this?
$INFO_LOW	This sets the lower value of the stat range.
$INFO_HI	This sets the higher value of the stat range.
$INFO_PRIORITY	Setting priority to 0 disables that stat event. The priority value is realtive to all the events qualified to start and their priorities. i.e. 3 mods with equal priority values all have the same chance regardless of the actual values.
$INFO_REMOVE	This will REMOVE a stat event. You will be prompted at least twice by Actor Events. The mod associated with the stat event can also take additional action.